now let's give the crocodile a grain
现在让我们给鳄鱼一粒麦粒
shading texture some of the techniques
着色纹理的一些技术
uses will be explained more in depth in
中将更深入地说明用法。
later lectures to shade the body I will
以后讲课要遮蔽身体我会
first combine the body parts I right
先把身体各部分组合起来，好吗？
click on the body and choose select same
单击正文，然后选择选择相同
fill color
填充颜色
then I go to path Union
然后我去Path Union
I call the United path body parts
我称联合之路为身体部位
I will drag the body parts path out of
我会将身体部位的路径拖出
the feed group above the feet I right
脚部上方的提要群组I右
click on the body parts path and choose
单击身体部位路径并选择
set clip group I name the clip group
设置剪辑组我为剪辑组命名
body shaving you can recognize a clip
身体剃须你能认出一个夹子
Group by a folder with a scissor sign
按带有剪刀标志的文件夹分组
when I open the body shading folder I
当我打开身体着色文件夹时
see a folder called clip whatever is in
查看名为Clip What is in的文件夹
this folder will be used as a clipping
此文件夹将用作剪辑
mask I want to reuse the body parts path
遮罩我想重复使用身体部位路径
so I press Ctrl d i drag the copy
因此我按下Ctrl d并拖动副本
outside the clip folder
在剪辑文件夹之外
and I duplicate it again
我又复制了一遍
with the rectangle tool I draw a
使用矩形工具，我绘制了一个
rectangle that is larger than the body
大于正文的矩形
parts
零件
I drag body parts above the rectangle
我将身体部位拖到矩形上方
then I press Ctrl 9 3 times
然后我按了Ctrl 9键3次
what I did is inset the path with three
我所做的是在路径中插入三个
steps I hold shift and also select the
按住Shift键并选择
rectangle I go to path difference I call
矩形我去路径差我叫
the result texture I close an open layer
生成纹理I闭合一个打开的层
too to get more room and open body
为了获得更多的空间和开放的身体
shading again I drag the fill and stroke
再次添加底纹我拖动填充和笔触
panel all the way to the bottom until I
面板一直到底部，直到我
see a blue blinking rectangle then I let
看到一个蓝色闪烁的矩形，然后我让
go of the mouse I click on texture at
松开鼠标，我点击纹理
the bottom of fill and stroke I increase
填充和描边的底部I增加
blur to about 30. I click on the black
模糊到大约30。我点击黑色
Swatch I go to filters overlays noise
色板我转到滤镜覆盖噪波
fill I click on the noise color Tab and
填充我单击噪波颜色选项卡，然后
set Alpha to zero then I click on
将Alpha设置为零，然后我点击
options I click on live preview for
我点击实时预览的选项
turbulence type I choose fractal noise
湍流类型I选择分形噪声
with horizontal and vertical frequency
具有水平和垂直频率
you can make the grain smaller and
你可以把颗粒变得更小
larger I click on apply at some parts I
较大的我在某些部分单击应用I
want more grain and at some parts less
想要更多的谷物，在某些地方想要更少
to do this I click on the Node tool
要执行此操作，请单击节点工具
right now there are 32 nodes I can drag
现在我可以拖动32个节点
which I find too many so I go to path
我发现太多了，所以我就走小路
simplify now I have 18 nodes which is
现在简化我有18个节点，
better I also lower the opacity of the
更好的是，我还降低了
texture I will set it to 25 percent now
纹理我现在将其设置为25%
I will adjust the visibility of the
我会调整
grain by dragging the nose
拖鼻子谷物